[
  {
    "question": "Where is the wine region of Tuscany located?",
    "choices": [
      "Portugal",
      "Italy",
      "Chile",
      "Germany"
    ],
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main grape used in Champagne?",
    "choices": [
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Chardonnay",
      "Pinot grigio",
      "Merlot"
    ],
    "answer": "Chardonnay"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where does Malbec originally come from?",
    "choices": [
      "Argentina",
      "Chile",
      "Spain",
      "France"
    ],
    "answer": "France"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a \"dry\" wine?",
    "choices": [
      "A wine with little to no sweetness",
      "Sparkling wine",
      "Sweet wine",
      "Fortified wine"
    ],
    "answer": "A wine with little to no sweetness"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the primary flavor you might taste in a Sauvignon Blanc?",
    "choices": [
      "Molasses",
      "Citrus",
      "Chocolate",
      "Apple"
    ],
    "answer": "Citrus"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the wine region of Rioja located?",
    "choices": [
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Germany",
      "France"
    ],
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main grape in most red wines from Tuscany’s Chianti region?",
    "choices": [
      "Sangiovese",
      "Syrah",
      "Cabernet Sauvignon",
      "Pinot Noir"
    ],
    "answer": "Sangiovese"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where does Riesling wine originate from?",
    "choices": [
      "Chile",
      "Portugal",
      "Germany",
      "Italy"
    ],
    "answer": "Germany"
  },
  {
    "question": "What French wine region is known for Riesling?",
    "choices": [
      "Bordeaux",
      "Provence",
      "Burgundy",
      "Alsace"
    ],
    "answer": "Alsace"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the wine region of Mendoza located?",
    "choices": [
      "Chile",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal",
      "Argentina"
    ],
    "answer": "Argentina"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of swirling wine in a glass?",
    "choices": [
      "To release aromas",
      "To mix flavors",
      "To release color",
      "To cool it down"
    ],
    "answer": "To release aromas"
  },
  {
    "question": "How is port wine different from most wines?",
    "choices": [
      "It’s made from one grape",
      "It’s sweet and fortified",
      "It’s aged in oak",
      "It’s sparkling"
    ],
    "answer": "It’s sweet and fortified"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the wine region of Marlborough located?",
    "choices": [
      "Chile",
      "France",
      "Portugal",
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "answer": "New Zealand"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the primary white grape in the Mosel region of Germany?",
    "choices": [
      "Pinot Noir",
      "Merlot",
      "Riesling",
      "Sauvignon Blanc"
    ],
    "answer": "Riesling"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is most associated with the Barolo wines of Piedmont, Italy?",
    "choices": [
      "Nebbiolo",
      "Dolcetto",
      "Sangiovese",
      "Barbera"
    ],
    "answer": "Nebbiolo"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the wine region of Stellenbosch located?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Portugal",
      "Germany",
      "South Africa"
    ],
    "answer": "South Africa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which region is famous for its Tempranillo grape?",
    "choices": [
      "Napa Valley",
      "Bordeaux",
      "Rioja",
      "Tuscany"
    ],
    "answer": "Rioja"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a key white grape grown in the Loire Valley of France?",
    "choices": [
      "Chardonnay",
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Syrah",
      "Pinot Noir"
    ],
    "answer": "Sauvignon Blanc"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the wine region of Barossa Valley located?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "Spain",
      "Portugal",
      "Chile"
    ],
    "answer": "Australia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the wine region of Douro Valley located?",
    "choices": [
      "Chile",
      "Germany",
      "Portugal",
      "France"
    ],
    "answer": "Portugal"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the primary grape in red wines from the Mendoza region of Argentina?",
    "choices": [
      "Merlot",
      "Cabernet Sauvignon",
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Malbec"
    ],
    "answer": "Malbec"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the wine region of Willamette Valley located?",
    "choices": [
      "Oregon",
      "Portugal",
      "Italy",
      "Spain"
    ],
    "answer": "Oregon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Screaming Eagle produced?",
    "choices": [
      "Sonoma Valley",
      "Washington State",
      "Portugal",
      "Napa Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Napa Valley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Harlan produced?",
    "choices": [
      "Italy",
      "Finger Lakes",
      "Spain",
      "Napa Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Napa Valley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Scarecrow produced?",
    "choices": [
      "Napa Valley",
      "Canada",
      "Chile",
      "Sonoma County"
    ],
    "answer": "Napa Valley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which red grape is key to the wines of Brunello di Montalcino in Italy?",
    "choices": [
      "Cabernet Sauvignon",
      "Pinot Noir",
      "Nebbiolo",
      "Sangiovese"
    ],
    "answer": "Sangiovese"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the wine region of Margaret River located?",
    "choices": [
      "Southern Italy",
      "Western Australia",
      "Western Portugal",
      "Northern California"
    ],
    "answer": "Western Australia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which red grape is central to the wines of Beaujolais, France?",
    "choices": [
      "Cabernet Sauvignon",
      "Syrah",
      "Gamay",
      "Sauvignon Blanc"
    ],
    "answer": "Gamay"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which parent company produces la Grande Dame Champagne?",
    "choices": [
      "Lurton",
      "Bertrand",
      "Veuve Cliquot",
      "Moet"
    ],
    "answer": "Veuve Cliquot"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the region of Stellenbosch located?",
    "choices": [
      "South Africa",
      "South Australia",
      "Southern Chile",
      "Southern Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "South Africa"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the 2 departments of Alsace?",
    "choices": [
      "North and South",
      "East and West",
      "Haut and Bas",
      "Sud and Ouest"
    ],
    "answer": "Haut and Bas"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is not a noble grape of Alsace?",
    "choices": [
      "Riesling",
      "Pinot Gris",
      "Muscat",
      "Merlot"
    ],
    "answer": "Merlot"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which region sits on the border of Germany?",
    "choices": [
      "Alsace",
      "Burgundy",
      "Bordeaux",
      "Jura"
    ],
    "answer": "Alsace"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region will you find Sélection de Grains Nobles on the label?",
    "choices": [
      "Alsace",
      "Burgundy",
      "Bordeaux",
      "Jura"
    ],
    "answer": "Alsace"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main red grape of Alsace?",
    "choices": [
      "Pinot Noir",
      "Cabernet Franc",
      "Poulsard",
      "Grenache"
    ],
    "answer": "Pinot Noir"
  },
  {
    "question": "Local specialties vin jaune and vin de paille can be found where?",
    "choices": [
      "Jura",
      "Champagne",
      "Burgundy",
      "Bordeaux"
    ],
    "answer": "Jura"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the region of L’Etoile?",
    "choices": [
      "Jura",
      "Champagne",
      "Burgundy",
      "Bordeaux"
    ],
    "answer": "Jura"
  },
  {
    "question": "What Champagne house is associated with Dom Perignon?",
    "choices": [
      "Drappier",
      "Moet & Chandon",
      "Selosse",
      "Veuve Cliquot"
    ],
    "answer": "Moet & Chandon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Santa Rita Hills AVA?",
    "choices": [
      "Oregon",
      "California",
      "New York",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "California"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is chapitalization?",
    "choices": [
      "Adding water to fermenting wine",
      "adding sugar to the fermenting wine",
      "taking water away from wine at bottling",
      "using a screw cap enclosure"
    ],
    "answer": "adding sugar to the fermenting wine"
  },
  {
    "question": "What contribution is Louis Pasteur responsible for?",
    "choices": [
      "harvest science",
      "varietal science",
      "water table management",
      "fermentation science"
    ],
    "answer": "fermentation science"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Algarve region?",
    "choices": [
      "South Africa",
      "South Australia",
      "Southern Chile",
      "Southern Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Southern Portugal"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main grape of the Gigondas region?",
    "choices": [
      "Pinot Noir",
      "Cabernet Franc",
      "Poulsard",
      "Grenache"
    ],
    "answer": "Grenache"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which region is known for their rosé production?",
    "choices": [
      "Bordeaux",
      "Burgundy",
      "Alsace",
      "Provence"
    ],
    "answer": "Provence"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which region is known for their Pinot Noir production?",
    "choices": [
      "Bordeaux",
      "Burgundy",
      "Alsace",
      "Provence"
    ],
    "answer": "Burgundy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is known for its resemblance to Cabernet Sauvignon?",
    "choices": [
      "Pinot Noir",
      "Cabernet Franc",
      "Poulsard",
      "Grenache"
    ],
    "answer": "Cabernet Franc"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Willamette Valley?",
    "choices": [
      "Oregon",
      "California",
      "New York",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "Oregon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Long Island AVA?",
    "choices": [
      "Oregon",
      "California",
      "New York",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "New York"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Sancerre located?",
    "choices": [
      "Loire Valley",
      "Bordeaux",
      "Burgundy",
      "Champagne"
    ],
    "answer": "Loire Valley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where would you find the 1855 classification?",
    "choices": [
      "Loire Valley",
      "Bordeaux",
      "Burgundy",
      "Champagne"
    ],
    "answer": "Bordeaux"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the McLaren Vale wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "South Africa",
      "South Australia",
      "Southern Chile",
      "Southern Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "South Australia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Hermitage region?",
    "choices": [
      "Rhône Valley",
      "Provence",
      "Champagne",
      "Loire Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Rhône Valley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Condrieu region?",
    "choices": [
      "Rhône Valley",
      "Provence",
      "Champagne",
      "Loire Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Rhône Valley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which region is La Grande Dame produced in?",
    "choices": [
      "Rhône Valley",
      "Provence",
      "Champagne",
      "Loire Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Champagne"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the region of Paarl?",
    "choices": [
      "South Africa",
      "South Australia",
      "Southern Chile",
      "Southern Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "South Africa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Columbia Valley AVA?",
    "choices": [
      "Oregon",
      "California",
      "New York",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "Washington State"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Red Mountain AVA?",
    "choices": [
      "Oregon",
      "California",
      "New York",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "Washington State"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Châteauneuf-du-Pape AOP?",
    "choices": [
      "Rhône Valley",
      "Provence",
      "Champagne",
      "Loire Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Rhône Valley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Vouvray region?",
    "choices": [
      "Rhône Valley",
      "Provence",
      "Champagne",
      "Loire Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Loire Valley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the city of Reims located?",
    "choices": [
      "Rhône Valley",
      "Provence",
      "Champagne",
      "Loire Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Champagne"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the city of Nice located?",
    "choices": [
      "Rhône Valley",
      "Provence",
      "Champagne",
      "Loire Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Provence"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Melon de Borgogne grape found?",
    "choices": [
      "Rhône Valley",
      "Provence",
      "Burgundy",
      "Loire Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Loire Valley"
  },
  {
    "question": "What grape is most associated with Napa Valley?",
    "choices": [
      "Cabernet Sauvignon",
      "Grenache",
      "Riesling",
      "Malbec"
    ],
    "answer": "Cabernet Sauvignon"
  },
  {
    "question": "What grape is most associated with Mendoza, Argentina?",
    "choices": [
      "Cabernet Sauvignon",
      "Grenache",
      "Riesling",
      "Malbec"
    ],
    "answer": "Malbec"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Schloss Johannisberg?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Germany",
      "Austria",
      "Hungary"
    ],
    "answer": "Germany"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which country is associated with Liebfraumilch?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Germany",
      "Austria",
      "Hungary"
    ],
    "answer": "Germany"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the region of Tokaj found?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Germany",
      "Austria",
      "Hungary"
    ],
    "answer": "Hungary"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where would you most likely find \"Doctor\" on a wine label?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Germany",
      "Austria",
      "Hungary"
    ],
    "answer": "Germany"
  },
  {
    "question": "What grape is most associated with the Rheingau?",
    "choices": [
      "Chardonnay",
      "Grenache",
      "Riesling",
      "Malbec"
    ],
    "answer": "Riesling"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Horse Heaven Hills AVA?",
    "choices": [
      "Oregon",
      "California",
      "New York",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "Washington State"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is most likely grown in a cooler climate?",
    "choices": [
      "Viognier",
      "Grenache",
      "Riesling",
      "Malbec"
    ],
    "answer": "Riesling"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is most likely grown near Grenache and Syrah vines?",
    "choices": [
      "Viognier",
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Nebbiolo",
      "Malbec"
    ],
    "answer": "Viognier"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an anbaugebiet?",
    "choices": [
      "German region",
      "Alsatian lake",
      "French mountians",
      "Oregon hills"
    ],
    "answer": "German region"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Wachau wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Germany",
      "Austria",
      "Hungary"
    ],
    "answer": "Austria"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is most associated with Pouilly-Fume?",
    "choices": [
      "Viognier",
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Nebbiolo",
      "Pinot Noir"
    ],
    "answer": "Sauvignon Blanc"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is mostly associated with the Barbaresco wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Merlot",
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Nebbiolo",
      "Pinot Noir"
    ],
    "answer": "Nebbiolo"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is mostly associated with the Medoc wine growing area?",
    "choices": [
      "Cabernet Sauvignon",
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Nebbiolo",
      "Pinot Noir"
    ],
    "answer": "Cabernet Sauvignon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Hawkes Bay wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "Chile"
    ],
    "answer": "New Zealand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Margaret River wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "Chile"
    ],
    "answer": "Australia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Pinotage grape most likley grown?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "South Africa"
    ],
    "answer": "South Africa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is most likely grown in Barossa Valley?",
    "choices": [
      "Vidal",
      "Shiraz",
      "Pinot Noir",
      "Pinotage"
    ],
    "answer": "Shiraz"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is most likely grown in McLaren Vale?",
    "choices": [
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Shiraz",
      "Pinot Noir",
      "Pinotage"
    ],
    "answer": "Shiraz"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Patagonia wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "Chile"
    ],
    "answer": "Argentina"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Maipo Valley wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "Chile"
    ],
    "answer": "Chile"
  },
  {
    "question": "What country is Almaviva produced in?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "Chile"
    ],
    "answer": "Chile"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Santorini wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Greece",
      "Hungary",
      "Romania",
      "Bulgaria"
    ],
    "answer": "Greece"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is botrytis cinerea?",
    "choices": [
      "a vineyard mushroom",
      "a fungus",
      "a yeast strain",
      "the Latin god of wine"
    ],
    "answer": "a fungus"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the VQA found?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "Canada"
    ],
    "answer": "Canada"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Lake Erie North Shore found?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "Canada"
    ],
    "answer": "Canada"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Valle de Guadalupe?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "Mexico",
      "Argentina",
      "Chile"
    ],
    "answer": "Mexico"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Coonawara wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand",
      "Argentina",
      "Chile"
    ],
    "answer": "Australia"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main grape used for the wines of Cornas?",
    "choices": [
      "Grenache",
      "Syrah",
      "Merlot",
      "Cabernet Sauvignon"
    ],
    "answer": "Syrah"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main grape used for the wines of Côte-Rôtie?",
    "choices": [
      "Grenache",
      "Syrah",
      "Merlot",
      "Cabernet Sauvignon"
    ],
    "answer": "Syrah"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main grape used for the wines of Gigondas?",
    "choices": [
      "Grenache",
      "Syrah",
      "Merlot",
      "Cabernet Sauvignon"
    ],
    "answer": "Grenache"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main grape used for the wines of Pomerol?",
    "choices": [
      "Grenache",
      "Syrah",
      "Merlot",
      "Cabernet Sauvignon"
    ],
    "answer": "Merlot"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which country would Crémant sparkling wines be found in?",
    "choices": [
      "Greece",
      "Hungary",
      "Romania",
      "France"
    ],
    "answer": "France"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which country would Sancerre be found in?",
    "choices": [
      "England",
      "Hungary",
      "Romania",
      "France"
    ],
    "answer": "France"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the German tern for \"dry\"?",
    "choices": [
      "grosslage",
      "trocken",
      "tresterbrand",
      "winzer"
    ],
    "answer": "trocken"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Pfalz wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Greece",
      "Hungary",
      "Germany",
      "France"
    ],
    "answer": "Germany"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Nahe wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Greece",
      "Hungary",
      "Germany",
      "France"
    ],
    "answer": "Germany"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Baden wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Greece",
      "Hungary",
      "Germany",
      "France"
    ],
    "answer": "Germany"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Franken wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Greece",
      "Hungary",
      "Germany",
      "France"
    ],
    "answer": "Germany"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Ahr wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Greece",
      "Hungary",
      "Germany",
      "France"
    ],
    "answer": "Germany"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the synonym for Pinot Noir in Germany?",
    "choices": [
      "Pinot Gris",
      "Spätburgunder",
      "Septime",
      "Johannisberg"
    ],
    "answer": "Spätburgunder"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Zemplén wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Greece",
      "Hungary",
      "Germany",
      "France"
    ],
    "answer": "Hungary"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is most associated with Vouvray?",
    "choices": [
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Chenin Blanc",
      "Chardonnay",
      "Pinot Gris"
    ],
    "answer": "Chenin Blanc"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is most associated with Sancerre?",
    "choices": [
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Chenin Blanc",
      "Chardonnay",
      "Pinot Gris"
    ],
    "answer": "Sauvignon Blanc"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is most associated with Champagne?",
    "choices": [
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Chenin Blanc",
      "Chardonnay",
      "Pinot Gris"
    ],
    "answer": "Chardonnay"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is most associated with Bordeaux?",
    "choices": [
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Chenin Blanc",
      "Chardonnay",
      "Pinot Gris"
    ],
    "answer": "Sauvignon Blanc"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which grape is most associated with Chablis?",
    "choices": [
      "Sauvignon Blanc",
      "Chenin Blanc",
      "Chardonnay",
      "Pinot Gris"
    ],
    "answer": "Chardonnay"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Valencia wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Ribera del Duero wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Rioja wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Rías Baixas  wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Priorat wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Barolo wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Brunello di Montalcino wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Barbaresco wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Amarone della Valpolicella wine from?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Friuli wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Chianti Classico wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is thecountry that Prosecco comes from?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the country you would most likely find Tempranillo in?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the country you would most likely find Sangiovese in?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the country you would most likely find Nebbiolo in?",
    "choices": [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Italy",
      "Portugal"
    ],
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Seneca Lake wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "UK",
      "New Zealand",
      "USA"
    ],
    "answer": "USA"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Yamhill-Carlton District wine region?",
    "choices": [
      "Australia",
      "UK",
      "New Zealand",
      "USA"
    ],
    "answer": "USA"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is San Luis Obispo County?",
    "choices": [
      "Oregon",
      "California",
      "New York",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "California"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Alexander Valley AVA?",
    "choices": [
      "Oregon",
      "California",
      "New York",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "California"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Sierra Foothills AVA?",
    "choices": [
      "Oregon",
      "California",
      "New York",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "California"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Anderson Valley AVA?",
    "choices": [
      "Oregon",
      "California",
      "New York",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "California"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Russian River Valley AVA?",
    "choices": [
      "Oregon",
      "California",
      "New York",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "California"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Columbia Gorge AVA?",
    "choices": [
      "New Mexico",
      "California",
      "New York",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "Washington State"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Walla Walla Valley AVA?",
    "choices": [
      "Oregon",
      "California",
      "New York",
      "Washington State"
    ],
    "answer": "Washington State"
  },
  {
    "question": "What grape is most associated with the Russian River Valley AVA?",
    "choices": [
      "Merlot",
      "Pinot Noir",
      "Grenache",
      "Cabernet Sauvignon"
    ],
    "answer": "Pinot Noir"
  },
  {
    "question": "What grape is most associated with the Calistoga AVA?",
    "choices": [
      "Zinfandel",
      "Pinot Noir",
      "Grenache",
      "Cabernet Sauvignon"
    ],
    "answer": "Cabernet Sauvignon"
  }
]